(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-16T23:22:23.879800",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
G-A-M-E
R-S
Okay!
Come on!
No!
G-A-M-E
R-S
Okay!
Come on!
No!
Are you ready?
Perfect!
G-A-M-E
R-S
Okay!
Come on!
ミオ！
Mio!
G-A-M-E-R-S
おかゆ！
Okayu!
ころね！
Korone!
ミオ！
Mio!
Are you ready? No!
フブキ！
Fubuki!
G-A-M-E-R-S
ミオ！
Mio!
G-A-M-E-R-S
おかゆ！
Okayu!
ころね！
Korone!
Are you ready?
フブキ！
Fubuki!
G-A-M-E-R-S
フブキ！
Fubuki!
ミオ！
Mio!
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment until the performance begins.
G-A-M-E-R-S
おかゆ！
Okayu!
ころね！
Korone!
Are you ready?
フブキ！
Fubuki!
G-A-M-E-R-S
Okay!
みお！
Mio!
G-A-M-E-R-S
Okay!
ころね
Korone
Are you ready?
フブキ
Fubuki
Ｇ・Ａ・Ｍ・Ｅ・Ｒ・Ｓ ゲーマーズ！
G-A-M-E-R-S, GAMERS!
おかゆ
Okayu
ミオ
Mio
Ｇ・Ａ・Ｍ・Ｅ・Ｒ・Ｓ ゲーマーズ！
G-A-M-E-R-S, GAMERS!
ころね
Korone
開演までしばらくお待ちください
[Please wait a moment until the performance begins]
公演ハッシュタグ #超ゲマズ2_day2
[Performance Hashtag: #ChoGemars2_day2]
Hey! Hey!
公演中の一部の時間帯に限り、スクリーンショット・SNSへの投稿OK
[Screenshots and SNS posts are OK during designated times only]
録画、録音、ミラー配信や違法アップロードは固く禁止いたします
[Recording, mirror streaming, and illegal uploads are strictly prohibited]
Are you ready?
ニャー！
Meow!
Let's go!
One...
Two!
Hey! Hey!
Are you ready?
ニャー！
Meow!
Let's go!
ホロライブゲーマーズ！
Hololive Gamers!
We are GAMERS!
おっと白上 登場 参上
Oops, here comes Shirakami! I have arrived!
白上キツネも耳白上 もばきです
I'm Shirakami Fox, with white ears, I'm Mobaki!
突っ込まないと始まらない 君もスタートに入力しなさい
It won't start unless you retort! Go ahead and enter at the start!
ハイテンション！ (イェイ！) ローテンション！ (イェイ！)
High tension! (Yay!) Low tension! (Yay!)
トトトトトトトトトトトト
To-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to
名に恥じないテクを今見せる おっぱいよりもゲームを取るお年頃
Showing off techniques worthy of my name! I'm at the age where I choose games over boobs!
ウチ！ウチ！ウチだよ！
Uchi! Uchi! It's me!
大神ミオだよ 黒髪ケモミミおおかみ
I'm Ookami Mio, the black-haired beast-eared wolf!
ツッコミでキメます ライトニングボルト
Hitting you with my retorts like a lightning bolt!
笑い出すと止まらない ゲラゲラ
Once I start laughing, I can't stop! Gela gela!
つまり実質ツッコミってこと？
So basically, I'm the straight man of the group?
壊して設置して 大暴れ
Destroying, placing, going wild!
タロット占いで導く未来 ほらゲーマーズやりたくなーい？
Guiding the future with tarot readings! Hey, don't you want to play games?
四人揃えばパーティ まずは太鼓を
When the four of us gather, it's a party! First, beat the drums!
君も朝までお遊戯が 進行中
Your playtime until morning is now in progress!
キーが滑るんで
Because my keys are slipping,
夜更かし目指してレベル上げ
aiming to stay up late, leveling up!
今日は何プレイしよう？
What shall we play today?
君のハートを攻略しちゃう
We're going to conquer your heart!
選択をしてシミュレーション
Make your choice and simulate!
初見も古参も大歓迎！
First-timers and long-time fans are all welcome!
やっぱゲームは楽しいね！
After all, games are so much fun!
We are GAMERS!
おにぎりおにぎり もぐもぐおかゆ
Onigiri, onigiri, munch munch, Okayu!
猫耳おにぎり はい スタート
Cat ears, onigiri, alright, start!
気まぐれフラフラ 嘘も愛のうちだもん
Whimsical and wandering, even lies are a part of love.
ねぇ 僕のこと見てるよね？
Hey, you're watching me, right?
まったりゆったり 跳ねるビートに乗って
Chilling and relaxing, riding on a bouncing beat,
全肯定するよ いい波乗って
I'll unconditionally accept you! Riding on a great wave,
全肯定肯定 効率オッケー
Unconditional acceptance, efficiency okay!
毎日僕と遊ぼうね
Play with me every day, okay?
おるよー！
I'm here!
指！指！わおーん！
Fingers! Fingers! Woof!
パンはころねころね 戌神ころね！
The bread is coronet-coronet, Inugami Korone!
今日も気合はキングチャールズ
Fired up today like a King Charles!
スーパーに流れる曲っぽくって言われるけど明るくハッピー
They say it sounds like supermarket BGM, but I'm bright and happy!
なまるイントネーション ワールドリアクション
My dialect intonation, global reactions!
まずは指を捧げてくれる？
First, will you offer me your fingers?
はい、信仰！
Yes, devotion!
わかったなら骨に肉オッケー
If you understand, bone-in meat is okay!
好物のレトロゲームお届け！
Delivering my favorite retro games to you!
四人揃えばパーティ まずは太鼓を
When the four of us gather, it's a party! First, beat the drums!
フラグが立てば即座に 復活中
Once a flag is triggered, we instantly respawn!
エイムを鍛えて狙い撃ち
Train your aim and shoot!
今日は何プレイしよう？
What shall we play today?
君のハートを回復しちゃう
We'll restore your heart!
バグを作るね この感情
Creating bugs, this emotion!
体験版からやめられない
We can't stop, starting from the demo version!
だってゲームが好きなんだもん
Because we love games!
おててをたたいて！コールアンドレスポンスの時間だよ！
Clap your hands! It's time for call and response!
大きな声でレスポンスしてね！
Make sure to respond with a loud voice!
マイクチェックもしちゃいますよー！
We're going to do a mic check too!
Are you ready?
せーの、こんこん！
One, two, kon-kon! (Kon-kon!)
みょん、みょん！
Myon, myon! (Myon, myon!)
もぐ、もぐ！
Mogu, mogu! (Mogu, mogu!)
ゆび、ゆび！
Yubi, yubi! (Yubi, yubi!)
せーの、こんこん！
One, two, kon-kon! (Kon-kon!)
みょん、みょん！
Myon, myon! (Myon, myon!)
もぐ、もぐ！
Mogu, mogu! (Mogu, mogu!)
ゆび、ゆび！
Yubi, yubi! (Yubi, yubi!)
四人揃えばパーティ まずは太鼓を
When the four of us gather, it's a party! First, beat the drums!
うまく行かなくっても コンティニュー
Even if things don't go well, continue!
全クリするまで 諦めない
We won't give up until we beat the game!
エンディングを 見に行こう
Let's go see the ending!
君のハートを攻略しちゃう
We're going to conquer your heart!
選択をしてシミュレーション
Make your choice and simulate!
初見も古参も大歓迎！
First-timers and long-time fans are all welcome!
やっぱゲームは楽しいね！
After all, games are so much fun!
We are GAMERS!
こうして さいたまスーパーアリーナに
And thus, to Saitama Super Arena...
私たちが訪れたってわけ！ シャキーン！
We have arrived! Ta-da!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
ころねちゃん！
Korone-chan!
さいたま！さいたま！
Saitama! Saitama!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
可愛い！
So cute!
ふぅー！
Woo!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
本日もいっぱいでございますな！
We have a full house today as well!
ありがたいですなぁ。
We're so grateful.
ありがたい、本当に。
We really are, indeed.
ということで！
So then!
始まりました、ホロライブゲーマーズフェス 超超超超ゲーマーズ Day 2 です！
The hololive GAMERS fes. Super Super Super Super Gamers Day 2 has begun!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
フゥー！
Woo!
ということで、皆さん！こんこんきーつね！
So, everyone! Kon kon kitsune!
こんこんきーつね！
Kon kon kitsune!
白上フブキです、どうも！なぜかゲーマーズの奥で動いてた妖精さんやってた白上よ。
I'm Shirakami Fubuki! For some reason, I was the fairy moving in the background of Gamers' songs.
よしよし、よしよし。
Good, good!
妖精さんだったんだ。
So you were a fairy.
「妖精さんやって」って言われてやりました。
They told me to act like a fairy, so I did.
レッスンの時にあんなの1回もしなかったじゃん！
You didn't do any of that during rehearsal!
なんか足した、突然あんなの。
She added that so suddenly.
さぁ、続いては！
Now, next up!
はい！うち、うち、うちだよ！
Yes! It's me, me, me!
大神ミオだよ！
I'm Ookami Mio!
ミオしゃー！うわー！
Mio-sha! Woo!
大神ミオの皆さん、今日も盛り上げよろしくお願いします！
To everyone who loves Ookami Mio, please help fire things up today too!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
おかしい、おかしい。
This is hilarious!
そして！
And!
はい！
Yes!
みんな行くよ？
Everyone, here we go?
もぐもぐ〜？
Mogu mogu~?
おかゆ〜！
Okayu~!
よくできました！どうも！
Well done! Hello!
ホロライブゲーマーズの猫又おかゆです！
I'm Nekomata Okayu from hololive Gamers!
今日もよろしくお願いします！あの、出禁にならないようにね...
Please treat me well today! Um, so I don't get banned...
頑張ります！はい！
I'll do my best! Yes!
出禁はヤバいよ。
Getting banned is bad.
そして！
And!
はい、みんな行くよ！
Yes, here we go, everyone!
ジャン、ケン... ポン！
Jan, ken... Pon!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
戌神ころねです！よろしくお願いします！
I'm Inugami Korone! Pleased to meet you!
はい、大谷翔平の次くらいに...
Yes, right after Shohei Ohtani...
ジャンケンだったよ。
It was rock-paper-scissors.
サザエさんよ！
I'm Sazae-san!
ダメだ、ダメだ。
No way, that's not it.
もう、ころねすきー、それでも全部平気だった？今、大丈夫だった？
So, Koronesuki, was that all fine? Were you guys okay?
イェーイ！
Yeah!
ついてこれてるみたい、みんな。
Seems everyone is keeping up.
大丈夫だった、さすがです。
They were okay, as expected.
ということで、改めまして、ホロライブゲーマーズフェス 超超超超ゲーマーズ Day 2 が、ここさいたまスーパーアリーナで開幕じゃー！
So, once again, the hololive GAMERS fes. Super Super Super Super Gamers Day 2 is starting right here at Saitama Super Arena!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
いや、なんと、Day 1、Day 2 合わせると、なんか3万、約3万5000人以上が！
Wow, amazingly, combining Day 1 and Day 2, some 30,000, approximately over 35,000 people...
えー！すごい！
Wow! Amazing!
ということで、今日の Day 2 は、なんか1万7000人くらいいるらしいですよ！
So, today for Day 2, there seem to be about 17,000 people here!
えー！すごい！
Wow! Amazing!
凄いです、本当に！
It's really amazing!
上のほうも、みんないますよ、あそこ！いっぱい！
Even up there at the top, everyone's there! So many!
フゥー！
Woo!
見えてる？そこ。
Can you see us from there?
見えてる！大丈夫です！
We can see you! You're doing great!
左右も見えてますかー？
Can people on the left and right see us?
イェーイ！
Yeah!
1回目はね、ミオがこれなかった...
For the first one, Mio couldn't make it...
国立代々木競技場第一体育館だったんですけども！
...to the Yoyogi National Gymnasium, but...
さらに今回は大きな、大きな大きな場所でやらせていただくことになりました！
this time, we get to do it in an even bigger, much bigger venue!
2回目をやらせていただいて本当に本当にありがとうございます！本当に良かった、4人でステージに立つことが出来ました！
Thank you so much for giving us a second opportunity! I'm so glad all four of us could stand on this stage!
よかった、よかった！
I'm so glad!
みんなのおかげです、ありがとうございます！
It's all thanks to everyone, thank you!
えー、さて改めまして、このイベントではですね、ゲームが大好きな我々を中心に、超超超...
Now, once again, this event features us, who love games, and some very...
超豪華なゲストの皆さんと、いろんなゲームタイトルに挑戦したり、
super gorgeous guests, taking on various game titles,
ライブパフォーマンスをお届けするプレミアムイベントとなっております！
and delivering live performances in this premium event!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
しかも今回ですね、もう皆さんお分かりかと思いますが、Day 1に引き続き、4人の...
And this time, as you all probably know, following Day 1, the four of us...
お揃い新衣装！イェーイ！
have matching new outfits! Yeah!
可愛い！
So cute!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
尻尾サービス、尻尾サービスね。
Tail service, tail service!
尻尾サービス中！
Tail service in progress!
さらにさらに、会場ではですね、一部撮影OKなパートがありますので、そちらもお楽しみに！ぜひ最後まで皆さん、盛り上がっていきましょう！
What's more, there will be a portion of the show where photography is allowed, so look forward to that! Let's keep the energy high until the very end, everyone!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
ありがとうございます！ということで、我々ゲーマーズからも、1人ずつ意気込みを言っていきたいと思います！まずはみおから！
Thank you very much! So, we Gamers would each like to share our determination! First up, Mio!
はい！
Yes!
えっとですね、昨日の意気込みで
Well, in yesterday's determination,
明日まで体調を崩さないように頑張るっていう風にね
I said I'd do my best not to fall ill until tomorrow...
言わせていただいたんですけれども
is what I said.
もう今日この会場にいて、ここのステージに立つということは
But today, since I'm already at this venue on this stage,
どんなに体調を崩そうとも帰れないということなので
it means no matter how much I fall ill, I can't go home!
やめて！体調崩すのやめて！
No, don't! Please don't fall ill!
頑張るから！
I'll do my best!
最後まで笑顔で走りきる！
I will run through to the very end with a smile!
頑張りたいと思います！
I want to do my best!
みんな一緒に盛り上がってこう！
Let's all get hyped up together!
続いては、おかゆ！
Next up, Okayu!
はい！
Yes!
まあ、昨日はね、
Well, yesterday,
逆打率3割を目標に、大谷翔平ね
I aimed for a "reverse batting average of .300" like Shohei Ohtani...
頑張ったんですけど、
and did my best,
ちょっと逆に頑張りすぎて、
but maybe I tried a bit too hard in the opposite way,
微妙にデキるになりかけたので、
and I almost ended up doing too well...
今日は、
so today,
ほどほどに、逆にほどほどに
moderately... the reverse of moderately,
楽しんでいきたいと思います。
I'd like to enjoy myself.
何割くらいなんですか？ほどほどは。
About what percentage is "moderately"?
2.5！
2.5!
昨日なんかどっちかっていうと白上たちすごい被害を被る内容を受けたんですけど
Yesterday, we Shirakamis ended up suffering quite a bit of damage...
なんかテイクシックスとかさ。
like being forced to do Take Six.
何々？何のこと？
What? What was that about?
テイクシックスやらされたりとかさ、
Being made to do Take Six and stuff.
とぼけてますからね、この猫。
She's playing dumb, this cat.
本当に、どんなんでしたっけ？
Really? What was it like again?
どんなんでしたっけ？
What was it like again?
「白上の3割だろ」っていうことやらされたんですけど！
I was made to do the "30% of white hair" thing!
どんなんでしたっけ？
What was it like again?
嫌です！やんないよ！
No way! I'm not doing it!
なんかファイトもスーパーアリーナで吹っ飛ばされたりとかさ！
And being blown away at the Saitama Super Arena!
ちゅっちゅめとことかさ。
And that kiss on the cheek.
可愛かった、可愛かった。
It was cute, it was cute.
高いよな。
It was high, wasn't it?
満足度は高かったです。
The satisfaction level was high.
はい、じゃあ大谷さんの話をしていた...
Okay, who was talking about Ohtani-san...
はい！
Yes!
コロネ！
Korone!
昨日はね、ちょっと「翔平のために」とか言ってて、
Yesterday, I was saying "for the sake of Shohei,"
一部のころねすきーがね、
and some of the Koronesuki
ピキピキピーマンになってたので、今日は、
became angry like "Pikipiki Piman," so today,
ころねすきーのために頑張ります！
I will do my best for the Koronesuki!
あー可愛い！
Oh, so cute!
喜んでるよ、みんな！
Everyone's happy!
あと、翔平ごめん！
Also, sorry Shohei!
謝った！
She apologized!
やめて！
Stop it!
はい、えーそして白上もですね、今日もですね、
Yes, and I, Shirakami, today as well,
たくさん、えー読み上げることが多いと思うんですけども、
have a lot of things to read out.
その間、あのこの3人がきっと
During that time, I'm sure these three
いっぱい面白おかしいことやってくれるんじゃないかと思いますので、
will do lots of funny and amusing things.
白上のお話に耳を貸しつつ、お目目はですね、
While keeping an ear out for what I say,
あの上の大きいモニターと、
please keep your eyes on the big screen above
そしてあの可愛い3人を見ていただいて、
and those three cute girls.
最後皆さまでね、笑って帰れるといいなと思ってますので、
I hope we can all go home with a smile at the end,
よろしくお願いします！
so thank you!
Thank you!
そう、そして昨日と今日行われる
Yes! And the "Cho Cho Cho Cho Gamers" event
「超超超超ゲーマーズ」は、
taking place yesterday and today
ABEMA PPVで生配信してます！
is streaming live on ABEMA PPV!
コメントのみんな、見えてる？
Everyone in the comments, can you see us?
コメント見えてるよー！
We can see the comments!
「翔平も見えてる」って草って。
Someone commented "I can see Shohei too", lol.
大谷さん「3割だろ」ってコメントも。
Also "30% batting average Ohtani" comments too.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
配信チケットは絶賛発売中です！
Streaming tickets are now on sale!
イベントが終わっても、8月4日（月）の23時59分まで、
Even after the event ends, until August 4th (Monday) at 23:59,
何回も見返すことができます！
you can watch it back as many times as you want!
購入特典として、DAY1とDAY2で異なるシチュエーションの
As a purchase bonus, a limited original voice drama
限定オリジナルボイスドラマがついてきます！
with different situations for DAY1 and DAY2 is included!
DAY1は「秘密の事前プロデュースボイス」！
DAY1 is "Secret Pre-Production Voice"!
秘密？秘密？
Secret? Secret?
そしてDAY2は「内緒の直後...」！
And DAY2 is "Secret Immediately After..."!
内緒？内緒ってどの程度内緒なんですか？
Secret? To what extent is it a secret?
「誰にも言っちゃ駄目だぞ」みたいなことですか？
Is it like "You can't tell anyone about this"?
なっております！
That's what it is!
はい、えーあとはですね、我々からの
Yes, and also, a live image
直筆メッセージ入りのライブ、ライブ画、ライブ画像ってなんだ。
with handwritten message... wait, what is a "live image"?
直筆メッセージ入りのライブ画像もついてきますので、
A live image with handwritten messages is also included,
ぜひチェックしてみてください！よろしくお願いします！
so please check it out! Thank you!
さらに、昨年行われました「超超超超ゲーマーズ」の
Furthermore, the digest of last year's
ダイジェストが、ABEMAプレミアムで公開中です！
"Cho Cho Cho Cho Gamers" is now available on ABEMA Premium!
昨年のね、楽しかったのちょっと見失わないように、
To not lose track of last year's fun,
この3人でも頑張らせていただきますので、
the three of us will do our best,
その様子いっぱい見てください！よろしくお願いします！
so please watch a lot of it! Thank you!
はい、さらにさらに！イベント後に
Yes. Furthermore! Pre-orders for
グッズの受注販売が開始します！
merchandise will begin after the event!
こちらの期間は7月21日の23時59分まで！
This period is until July 21st at 23:59!
サイバーグッズストアにて受付中で、10月中旬頃からお届けです！
Accepting orders at Cyber Goods Store, shipping from around mid-October!
こちらも予約したよっていう人いますか？
Anyone here who has pre-ordered?
お、結構いるいる。
Oh, quite a lot of people!
結構買っちゃってんじゃない？
Haven't you bought quite a bit?
買ってるけど、みんなほら予約してるって。事後通販ありがとうございます！
They've bought them, but look, they're pre-ordering. Thank you for using post-event sales!
はい、えーそしてですね、当日販売のグッズは、
Yes, and we've heard that all
すべて売り切れと聞いております！皆様ありがとうございました！
same-day sales merchandise is sold out! Thank you very much, everyone!
え？どういうこと？
Eh? What do you mean?
びっくりしました、皆様本当に。
I was really surprised, everyone.
ランダムで推しをゲットできたかい？
Did you get your favorite character randomly?
できた！できた！
I did! I did!
できた？できた？よかった！ありがとうございます！
You did? You did? That's great! Thank you very much!
もしゲットできなかったという方がいらっしゃいましたらね
If anyone wasn't able to get them,
是非ともね事後通販で受注販売しておりますのでゲットしてください！
please grab yours during the post-event mail-order made-to-order sales!
そしてさらに さらに さらに！
And further, further, further!
もうご存知の方もいらっしゃると思いますが
Some of you may already know,
NTTドコモさんのhome 5Gとコラボキャンペーン実施中です！
but we are holding a collaboration campaign with NTT Docomo's home 5G!
あ、し、ましただね、これ。実施終わっちゃったんだ。
Ah, we did, actually. The campaign has already ended.
デカタオルや 入り口でもらえるうちわ 皆さんゲットしましたか？ ちゃんと「やりましたよ」って人！
Did everyone get the giant towel and the fan given out at the entrance? Let me see who did!
お、いらっしゃいます、ありがとうございます！
Oh, I see you! Thank you very much!
あ、ぎりぎり？
Ah, barely made it?
熱中症対策を万全にして、最後までお楽しみください！
Please take proper precautions against heatstroke and enjoy to the very end!
ありがとうございます。
Thank you so much.
あ、すみません！
Ah, excuse me!
こちらですね、事後限定グッズとしまして アクリルパネルが そういえば追加されてるんですよ！皆さん、知ってました？
Speaking of which, we actually added acrylic panels as post-event exclusive goods! Did everyone know that?
そう、実はアクリルパネル！
Yes, actually, acrylic panels!
こちらね、事後限定グッズなので、今「あ、そういえば！」って思った方は、是非とも！
Since these are post-event exclusives, if you just thought, "Oh, right!", please do!
あの、あの、是非ゲットしてください！
Um, um, please make sure to get them!
あの、あの、やめて！
Um, um, stop!
ごめんなさい！
I'm sorry!
まだまだ、次ありますからね！
We still have more for you!
我々ゲーマーズを応援したいという声が多かったので、今回のイベントで「チアスポット」さんとのコラボ決定ー！イェーイ！
Since so many of you wanted to support Gamers, we've decided on a collaboration with CheerSPOT! Yay!
誰でも簡単に、ここチアスポットの場所に、我々の応援広告を出すことができます！
Anyone can easily put up our support advertisements here on CheerSPOT!
是非ともね、これ、白上も割と、日頃利用させていただいておりますので、とっても嬉しいですね。
Shirakami uses this quite often herself, so I'm really happy.
使ってるの？使ってる。めちゃめちゃ嬉しい。
You use it? Yes, I do. I'm so happy.
この会場内にもですね、設置してあるのを見たと思うんですけど、あんな感じでですね、すごく綺麗に広告出せますので、よければよろしくお願いします。
You probably saw it set up inside the venue too, but you can display advertisements beautifully like that, so please support us if you'd like.
えー、さらに！さいたまスーパーアリーナ会場内で、等身大を初お披露目させていただきました！
Furthermore, we unveiled our life-sized figures for the first time inside Saitama Super Arena!
3月のエキスポ会場で発表された、フブミオ！等身大に続きまして、おかころのフィギュアも発表されました！見てくれましたか？
Following FubuMio announced at March's EXPO, OkaKoro's figures were also announced! Did you check them out?
見てくれました！
We did!
可愛い！可愛い！
So cute! Cute!
また、昨日から新作フィギュアが、デザインココから受注開始ということで、皆さん、予約したか？しろ！
Also, reservations for the new figures from Design COCO started yesterday, so did everyone pre-order? Do it!
めっちゃ可愛かった、めっちゃ可愛かった。まじ可愛かった。
They were super cute, super cute. Seriously cute.
イベントの開催を記念しまして、8月7日までに、ココストアで予約してくれた方には、特典のステッカープレゼントだそうです！
To commemorate this event, those who pre-order on COCO Store by August 7th will receive a bonus sticker!
欲しい！欲しい！
I want it! Want it!
そしてね、おかころも出たんですけど、フブミオが「終わっちゃった...」と思ってたんですが、なんと！期間限定で、フブミオの追加予約も開始してます！
And though OkaKoro has been released, for those who thought FubuMio's reservations were over... FubuMio's additional pre-orders have also started for a limited time!
最高！最高！
Awesome! The best!
お願いします！是非ともゲーマーズ4人揃えれる方は揃えてみろ！
Please! For those who can collect all four Gamers, try to collect them all!
揃えてみろ！
Try to collect them!
そして最後に、カンダフル様による、協賛企業グッズ！超超超超ポップコーンと、超超超超グリルチキンです！
And lastly, collaborative goods from Candalf! Super-super-super-super popcorn and super-super-super-super grilled chicken!
チキン！チキン！
Chicken! Chicken!
今回のイベントのキービジュアルが、全面に出たデザインとなっているとのことでして、ポップコーンは税込1,000円、チキンは税込1,500円で販売です。
The design features the key visual of this event all over. Popcorn is 1,000 yen tax incl., and chicken is 1,500 yen tax incl.
ポップコーンは塩キャラメル味、チキンはグリルチキンになってます！イェーイ！
Popcorn is salted caramel flavor, and the chicken is grilled chicken! Yay!
これ、ポップコーンの方にはランダムトレカが付いているそうなので、よろしくお願いします。
Apparently, the popcorn comes with a random trading card, so please check it out.
食べてる、食べてる。
They are eating it, eating it.
美味しい、美味しい。
Delicious, delicious.
なんと！サイバーグッズストアでは、こちらのポップコーンとチキンが、完売になってしまった！
And amazingly! In the Cyber Goods Store, this popcorn and chicken have sold out!
えー！
Eh?!
なん、ですけど！
However!
なんと本日22時から追加販売が決定しました！
Actually, additional sales have been decided starting tonight at 22:00!
やったー！カンダフル！
Hooray! Candalf!
え、こちらのグッズはですね、他のグッズと異なりまして、受注販売ではなく数量限定商品のため、ご注意ください！
Please note that unlike other goods, these items are not made-to-order but are in limited quantities!
お願いします！サイバーグッズストアのほかに、カンダフルの公式通販サイトでも販売してますので、皆さんチェックお願いします。
Please! Besides the Cyber Goods Store, they are also sold on Candalf's official online store, so please check it out.
はい。集合アクリルパネルも含めてですね、事後でしか購入できないグッズなので、皆さん、是非確認してください！
Yes. Including the group acrylic panel, these are goods you can only buy post-event, so please make sure to check them out!
なんか、すごいデジャヴなんだけど、あれ？なんかデジャヴ...
I'm getting a huge sense of deja vu, wait. A sense of deja vu...
戻っておいで、ゲーマーズ列車の時間だよ、ほら。
Come back, it's time for the Gamers train, come on.
あ、出発、出発、出発。
Ah, departure, departure, departure.
フブミオ駅、フブミオ駅。
FubuMio Station, FubuMio Station.
乗らなきゃ、乗らなきゃ。
Have to get on, have to get on.
出発、出発。
Departure, departure.
いらっしゃい。
Welcome.
まもなく発車。
Departing shortly.
終点、終点。終わっちゃった。
Terminus, terminus. It's over.
えー、また昨日に引き続きまして、本日も韓国でのライブビューイングが開催されてます！
Also, following yesterday, a live viewing is being held in South Korea today as well!
韓国の皆さん、見てますか？
Everyone in Korea, are you watching?
ヨロブン、アンニョンハシムニカ！サランハムニダ！
Everyone, hello! I love you!
韓国の方もですね、終わった後とか始まる前とかに、やっぱ集合写真いっぱい撮ってくださってて、ポスト確認させていただきました。今日もよろしくお願いします！
Those in Korea have been taking lots of group photos after and before the show, and I've been checking your posts. Thank you for your support today as well!
サランヘヨ！
I love you!
さあ、では早速ですね、最初に送る...
Now, let's get right into the first...
ゲームタイトル発表しちゃいましょうかね！
Shall we announce the game title?
はい！
Yes!
はい、じゃあいってみましょう！
Okay, let's go!
せーの！
Ready, set...
どうぞー！
Go ahead!
ギャングビースツ！
Gang Beasts!
はい、こちらはゼリーのようにぐにゃぐにゃなキャラクターたちが
This is a game where floppy, jelly-like characters...
危険なステージでドタバタバトルロイヤルを繰り広げる
...engage in a chaotic battle royale on dangerous stages.
ちょっとおバカなマルチプレイヤーパーティーゲームです！
It's a silly multiplayer party game!
今回は２対２のチーム戦と、
This time, we'll face off in a 2v2 team match...
個人戦の２マッチで対決したいと思います！
...and a free-for-all match, spanning two matches!
イェーイ！
Yay!
こちら勝利すると、頭の後ろに星のバルーンが付きます。
If you win, a star balloon will float behind your head.
最終的にバルーンが一番多い人が勝利となります！
Ultimately, the person with the most balloons wins!
ということで、さっそくやっていきましょう！
So, let's get right into it!
おおー！ / ゴーゴー！
Let's go, go, go!
第１マッチは２対２のチーム戦ということで、
Since the first match is a 2v2 team battle...
チームはですね、先ほどあみだで決めました！
...the teams were decided earlier by lottery!
フブおかチームと、
Team Fubu-Oka...
みおころチーム！
...and Team Mio-Koro!
はい！
Yes!
ということで、フブおか、神様、仏様、フブおか！
So, Fubu-Oka... God, Buddha, Fubu-Oka!
イェーイ！
Yay!
合ってるかな？
Did we get that right?
たぶんギリギリ合ってる。
Probably barely right.
ということで、対決してたいと思います！
Anyway, we're going to face off!
あの、そちら、なんか、ないんですか？
Um, don't you guys have something?
え？何がですか？
Eh? Like what?
え、掛け声とか、チーム名とか？
Like a battle cry or a team name?
ありますよ！
We do have one!
え、じゃあ教えてください。
Oh, then show us!
まずは...
First...
お姉ちゃんのおかゆと！
...big sister Okayu...
お、お、あ、い、い...
O-O-Ah-I-I...
妹のフブキちゃんでーす！
...and little sister Fubukichan!
お、お、あ、いい、いい。
O-O-Ah-I-I...
二人合わせて、ヤングコーン姉妹！
Together we are, the Young Corn Sisters!
え？ヤングコーン？
Eh? Young Corn?
ヤングコーンですか？
Young Corn?
ダメです！
Denied!
ダメだな。なんか弱そうな名前じゃない？
No way. Doesn't that sound weak?
なんかちょっと嫌がられてるかも。
Maybe they're a bit repulsed by it.
ほらほら、後ろにコントローラーがあるから。
Look, look! The controllers are behind us.
あ、はい、持ちます、持ちます。
Ah, yes! Let's grab them.
自分のカラー取ってね、ちゃんと。
Make sure to take your own color.
はい。これかな？
Yes. Is it this one?
はい、ということで、コントローラーでやっていきたいと思います。
Alright, let's get ready with the controllers.
では、ゲーム画面切り替えておいてください！
Now, please switch to the game screen!
何か、二人両手挙げてますけど。
Wait, why are they raising both hands?
これ誰が誰だか、全然わからない。 / じゃあ、自己紹介しよう。
I have no idea who is who. / Then let's introduce ourselves.
この青い白衣着てるのが、どうやら私、白上さんのようです。
The one in the blue lab coat seems to be me, Shirakami.
そして、そのお隣の猫の被り物を被ってるのが、僕です。
And next to her, the one wearing the cat headgear is me.
ええと、真っ赤っかな猫耳っぽいのがあるのが、うちです。大神ミオです。
The one in bright red with cat ears is me, Ookami Mio.
「シャキーン！」ってなってるのが、ころね。
The one going "Sha-keen!" is Korone.
「シャキーン！」みたいなやつ。
The "Sha-keen!" one.
ということで、まずはチーム戦でございます。準備はいいですか？
So, first is the team battle. Are you ready?
おお！ / はい！
Yes!
それでは、ギャングビースト、１回戦スタート！
Then, Gang Beasts Round 1, start!
やるぞ、やるぞ！ / 頑張ろう！
Let's do this! / Let's do our best!
大丈夫か？これ。 / 頑張る！ / 私たちの力を見せてやろう。
Is this gonna be okay? / We'll try! / Let's show them our power.
いけるのか？ / いけるよ！
Can we do this? / We can!
負けない。
We won't lose.
ほら！ / 叩け、叩け！
Take this! / Hit them, hit them!
やめろ！ / やばい、やばい！
Stop it! / Oh no, oh no!
あれ、誰？ / 強い！
Wait, who is that? / They're strong!
やばい、やばい！
Oh no, oh no!
はっ！はっ！はっ！
Ha! Ha! Ha!
やめろー！
Stop it!
何これ？なんか落ちそう、落ちそう。
What is this? I'm gonna fall!
やめろー！ / やばい、やばい！
Stop it! / Oh no, oh no!
こら！こら！ / 降りろ！
Hey! Hey! / Get off!
やばい、やばい！
Oh no, oh no!
やばい、やばい！ / うおお！
Oh no, oh no! / Uwooo!
頑張れ、フブキ！ / うおお！
Go, Fubuki! / Uwooo!
ほら！
Take this!
やばいやばいやばい！ / ころねが...
Oh no, oh no! / Korone is...
手伝って！ / おかゆ、どこ？
Help me! / Okayu, where are you?
手伝って！ / おお、うわあ！
Help me! / Oh, whoa!
何やってんだよ！
What are you doing?!
待って！ / 落ちちゃった。
Wait! / I fell.
待って！ / やばい、やばい！
Wait! / Oh no, oh no!
引きずり込まれちゃう！
I'm being dragged in!
やったー！勝ったー！
We did it! We won!
ああ、悔しい！
Ah, so frustrating!
でも、これ２先なので、２回勝ったチームが勝利ですからね！
But this is first-to-two, so the first team to win twice wins!
なんかくっついた！星だ！
Something stuck to us! It's a star!
星だ、星だ！
A star! A star!
じゃあ、２回戦いきますよ！
Then, let's head into Round 2!
よし、待て待て、待て待て！
Okay, wait, wait, wait, wait!
大神ミオ！
Ookami Mio!
くらえ、くらえ！
Take this, take this!
おらおらおらおら！
Ora ora ora ora!
いいよいいよ、いいよ！
Nice, nice, nice!
いやー！
Nooo!
おっと、あぶない！
Whoops, watch out!
よし！落ちた！
Yes! She fell!
落ちたー！
She fell!
ブルーの勝利！勝ったー！
Blue wins! We did it!
対戦決まった！
The match is decided!
よしよしよし！
Yes, yes, yes!
数の暴力やばい！
The violence of numbers is crazy!
痛いー！次はがんばる！
Ouch! We'll do better next time!
あそこにもち込もう
Let's drag them over there.
ピンチだぞ、これ！
We're in a pinch here!
おら！
Take that!
やばいやばいやばい！
Oh no, oh no, oh no!
いやー！
Nooo!
おちるー！
I'm falling!
それも落ちるよ！
That one's falling too!
それも道連れだ！
I'm taking you down with me!
おらー！あぶない！
Take that! Watch out!
きゃー！
Kyaaa!
いやー！どっちだ！？
Nooo! Which one is it?!
落ちる！落とした！
I'm falling! I dropped them!
あぶない！
Watch out!
いやー！
Nooo!
逃げろー！
Run!
扉から逃げようとしてる！
She's trying to escape through the door!
わー！
Waaa!
おちた！おちるおちる！
She fell! Falling, falling!
おかゆ！
Okayu!
あ、みお！あぶない！
Ah, Mio! Watch out!
穴に落ちるよ！
You'll fall in the hole!
きゃー！
Kyaaa!
あぶないあぶない！
Watch out, watch out!
よし！
Yes!
おかゆみお！ひっぱれ！
Okayu, Mio! Pull!
いやー！早く早く！
Nooo! Hurry, hurry!
がんばれ！
Do your best!
いやー！
Nooo!
助けてー！
Help me!
おかゆ！それおかゆ！
Okayu! That's Okayu!
あぶない！
Watch out!
うわー！ひっぱれ！
Waaa! Pull!
おかゆ落ちる！
Okayu is falling!
いやー！
Nooo!
おかゆー！みおー！
Okayu! Mio!
どっちだ！？
Which one is it?!
落ちるー！
I'm falling!
いやー！おらー！
Nooo! Take that!
あぶない！
Watch out!
やばいやばい！
Oh no, oh no!
おらおらおら！いけいけ！
Ora ora ora! Go go!
いやー！
Nooo!
落ちたー！勝ったー！
Fell! We won!
やったー！強い！
Yay! So strong!
対戦決まった！
The match is decided!
道連れのみおちゃんだ
Mio got dragged down too.
おもしろいなこれ
This is so fun.
やったー！
Yay!
負けたよ... そう！
We lost... Yes!
はい、ということで！
Alright, and with that...
バルーンの数は？
The number of balloons is...
え、負けた？
Eh, we lost?
バルーンの数は... 1, 2...
The number of balloons is... 1, 2...
これ勝つと少ないの？
Do you get fewer when you win?
3, 4...
4個！
4 balloons!
二人合わせて4個？
Both of us combined have 4?
4個です！
Yes, we have 4!
対する私たちは？こっち102個！
Meanwhile, we have... 102!
ということで今回は...
So, this time...
白上・猫又の勝ち！
Shirakami and Nekomata win!
やったー！
Yay!
負けちゃったよー
We lost...
残念ですが、ここで、お知らせでございます！
It's unfortunate, but we have an announcement here!
あ、そっか。バイバーイ！
Ah, that's right. Bye-bye!
早い早い！
Too fast!
無料配信をご覧の皆さまはここまでとなります！
For everyone watching the free broadcast, this is the end!
続きを観たい方はぜひ、ABEMA PPVにてチケットの購入をお願いいたします！
If you want to watch the rest, please purchase a ticket on ABEMA PPV!
よろしくお願いいたします！
Thank you!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
そうだよね、このあと個人戦が待ってますからね
That's right, the individual matches are waiting next!
バチバチにやっていきたいと思います！
We're going to fight intensely!
それでは！
And with that...
またねー！
See you!
【無料パートは終了いたしました】全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
[The free portion has ended] Watch the full event on ABEMA PPV!
ミオ！
Mio!
フブキ！
Fubuki!
G-A-M-E-R-S
おかゆ！
Okayu!
ころね！
Korone!
Are you ready?
フブキ！
Fubuki!
G-A-M-E-R-S
おかゆ！
Okayu!
ミオ！
Mio!
G-A-M-E-R-S
無料パートは終了いたしました
全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
[The free part of the stream has ended]
[You can watch the full stream on ABEMA PPV!]
G-A-M-E-R-S
おかゆ
Okayu
配信の詳細はQRコードをチェック！
[Scan the QR code for stream details!]
ころね
Korone
豪華購入特典あり！
[Exclusive purchase benefits included!]
みお
Mio
オリジナルボイスドラマと
限定直筆メッセージ入りライブ画像
[Original Voice Drama &]
[Live Photo with a handwritten message]
Are you ready?
みお
Mio
おかゆ
Okayu
G-A-M-E-R-S
フブキ
Fubuki
みお
Mio
G-A-M-E-R-S
おかゆ
Okayu
無料パートは終了いたしました
全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
The free portion of the stream has ended.
The full stream is available on ABEMA PPV!
ころね
Korone!
無料パートは終了いたしました
全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
The free portion of the stream has ended.
The full stream is available on ABEMA PPV!